Alan Rafkin Papers
Alan Rafkin Papers
- Scripts
  - One Day At a Time
    - 0402 Father Dear Father part 2 (Box 8)
    - 0403 Ann's Friends (Box 8)
    - 0404 Schneider's Helper (Box 8)
    - 0405 Bob's New Girl (Box 8)
    - 0406 Ann's Dating Game (Box 8)
    - 0407 Yes Sir That's My Baby (Box 8)
    - 0408 Jealousy part 1 (Box 8)
    - 0409 Jealousy part 2 (Box 8)
    - 0410 The Arab Connection (Box 8)
    - 0411 Peabody's War (Box 8)
    - 0412 The Married Man part 1 (Box 8)
    - 0413 The Married Man part 2 (Box 8)
    - 0414 The Married Man part 3 (Box 8)
    - 0415 Hold the Mustard (Box 8)
    - 0416 Girl Talk (Box 8)
    - 0417 Francine Strikes Again (Box 8)
    - 0418 Going Nowhere (Box 8)
    - 0419 The Piano Teacher (Box 8)
    - 0420 The Dental Hygienist (Box 9)
    - 0422 Mad For Each Other (Box 9)
    - 0423 The Broken Nose (Box 9)
    - 0425 Schneider Gets Fired (Box 9)
    - 0426 Grandma Leaves Grandpa (Box 9)
    - 0501 Back To School (Box 9)
    - 0502 Pressure (Box 9)
    - 0503 Julie's Wedding part 1 (Box 9)
    - 0504 Julie's Wedding part 2 (Box 9)
    - 0505 Between Mother and Daughter (Box 9)
    - 0506 Home Again Home Again (Box 9)
    - 0507 Small Wonder (Box 9)
    - 0508 Et Tu Ann (Box 9)
    - 0509 A Little Larceny (Box 9)
    - 0510 The Heart Attack (Box 9)
    - 0511 Schneider The Model (Box 9)
    - 0512 Male Jealousy (Box 9)
    - 0513 Happy New Year II (Box 9)
    - 0514 No Laughing Matter (Box 9)
    - 0515 So Long Mom (Box 9)
    - 0516 Triple Play (Box 9)
    - 0517 Old Horizons (Box 9)
    - 0518 Grecian Yearn (Box 9)
    - 0519 Endless Elliot (Box 9)
    - 0520 Girl With a Past (Box 9)
    - 0521 The Perils of Plastic (Box 9)
    - 0522 Pen Pals (Box 9)
    - 0523 The Spirit Is Willing (Box 9)
    - 0408 Jealousy part 1 (Box 9)
    - 0409 Jealousy part 2 (Box 9)
    - 0602 The Amarillo Connection (Box 9)
    - 0603 Ann Meets Nick part 1 (Box 9)
    - 0604 Ann Meets Nick part 2 (Box 9)
    - 0605 Farewell My Suite (Box 9)
    - 0606 The Merry Widow (Box 9)
    - 0607 The Drop Out (Box 9)
    - 0608 A Shot In the Dark (Box 9)
    - 0609 I Do I Do (Box 9)
    - 0610 Sunday Father (Box 9)
    - 0611 November Song parts 1/2 (Box 9)
    - 0613 Five Fingered Discount (Box 9)
    - 0614 A Tiny Romance (Box 9)
    - 0615 Out Of Bounds (Box 9)
    - 0616 Once a Mom (Box 9)
    - 0617 Caveat Emptor (Box 9)
    - 0618 Wicked Ann (Box 9)
    - 0619 The Indianapolis Story (Box 9)
    - 0620 Alex's Project (Box 9)
    - 0621 Small Wonder Returns (Box 9)
    - 0622 It's In the Cards (Box 9)
    - 0623 Airport (Box 9)
    - 0624 Stick 'Em Up (Box 9)
    - 0701 Alex Moves In (Box 9)
    - 0702 Shake Hands At the Bell (Box 9)
    - 0703 Hardball (Box 9)
    - 0704 Gift Horses (Box 9)
    - 0705 Julie Shows Up part 1 (Box 9)
    - 0706 Julie Shows Up part 2 (Box 9)
    - 0707 Plain Favorite (Box 9)
    - 0708 Alex's First Love (Box 9)
    - 0709 Dinner At Seven part 1 (Box 9)
    - 0710 Dinner At Seven part 2 (Box 10)
    - 0711 The Not So Silent Partner (Box 10)
    - 0712 Meow Meow (Box 10)
    - 0713 Ann the Failure (Box 10)
    - 0714 The Defector (Box 10)
    - 0715 Barbara's Crisis (Box 10)
    - 0716 Grandma's Nest Egg (Box 10)
    - 0717 Diamonds Are Forever (Box 10)
    - 0718 Mrs. O'Leary's Kid (Box 10)
    - 0719 Hear Today Gone Tomorrow (Box 10)
    - 0720 Orville and Emily Strike Back (Box 10)
    - 0721 Vegas part 1 (Box 10)
    - 0722 Vegas part 2 (Box 10)
    - 0723 Auntie Francine (Box 10)
    - 0724 Catcher in the Mud (Box 10)
    - 0801 Last Time I Saw Paris (Box 10)
    - 0802 The Honeymoon Is Over (Box 10)
    - 0803 The Hero (Box 10)
    - 0804 A Perfect Wedding part 1 (Box 10)
    - 0805 The Perfect wedding part 2 (Box 10)
    - 0806 Spare the Child (Box 10)
    - 0807 The Miracle Of Birth part 1 (Box 10)
    - 0808 The Miracle Of Birth part 2 (Box 10)
    - 0809 Lovers and Other Parents (Box 10)
    - 0810 First Things first (Box 10)
    - 0811 Pride and Privacy part 1 (Box 10)
    - 0812 Pride and Privacy part 2 (Box 10)
    - 0813 Pride and privacy part 3 (Box 10)
    - 0814 The Good Life (Box 10)
    - 0815 The Cruise (Box 10)
    - 0816 A Young Man's Fancy (Box 10)
    - 0817 Social Insecurity (Box 10)
    - 0818 Sonny-Boy (Box 10)
    - 0819 Buyer's Remorse (Box 10)
    - 0820 The Sisters (Box 10)
    - 0821 The Letter (Box 10)
    - 0823 Second Time Around (Box 10)
    - 0824 Honeymoon II (Box 10)
  - The Partridge Family
    - 3327 One More For the Road (Box 10)
  - Pistols 'N' Petticoats
    - 27508 Wretched Beautiful (Box 10)
    - 27512 The Great Gift (Box 10)
  - The Prime of Life
    - [no title] (Box 10)
  - Puppetman
    - [no title] (Box 10)
  - Re-Election Recollections
    - [no title] (Box 10)
  - Regular Joe
    - 101600 An Earful (Box 10)
    - 102600 Once A Bum (Box 10)
    - 103600 The Medium (Box 10)
  - Rhoda
    - 4154 I'll Be Loving You Sometimes (Box 10)
    - 74151 Home Is Where The Hard-Hat Is (Box 10)
    - [no number] Brenda's Makeover (Box 10)
  - Sam
    - [no title] (Box 10)
  - Sanford and Son
    - 0414 Julio and Sister and Nephew (Box 10)
    - 0422 The Older Woman (Box 10)
    - 0423 The Stung (Box 10)
    - 0505 Divorce Sanford Style (Box 10)
    - 0506 Bank On This (Box 10)
    - 0507 The TV Addict (Box 10)
    - 0519 Lamont In Love (Box 11)
    - 0520 The Escorts (Box 11)
    - 0522 A Pain In the Neck (Box 11)
    - 0523 Camping Trip (Box 11)
    - 0524 The Director (Box 11)
    - 0601 Fred's Extra Job (Box 11)
    - 0602 I Dream Of Choo Choo Rabinowitz (Box 11)
    - 0603 The Winning Ticket (Box 11)
    - 0604 The Hawaiian Connection part 1 (Box 11)
    - 0605 The Hawaiian Connection part 2 (Box 11)
    - 0609 Aunt Esther Has a Baby (Box 11)
    - 0613 Carol (Box 11)
  - Seinfeld
    - The Scoop (Box 3A)
  - The Shakiest Gun in the West
    - 2006 (Box 11)
  - She's the Sheriff
    - 176705 Lover Boy (Box 11)
  - Sisters
    - 5646 (Pilot) (Box 11)
  - The Situation At Hand
    - [no title] (Box 11)
  - The Sixth Sense Story proposal
    - [no title] (Box 11)
  - So Long Stanley
    - [no title] (Box 11)
  - Suddenly Susan
    - 225509 First Date (Box 3A)
    - 225510 Gay Parade, The (Box 3A)
    - Cast and crew list (Box 3A)
  - The Super
    - 44113 Flesh On the Third Floor (Box 11)
  - That Girl
    - [no number] Those Friars (Box 11)
  - That's My Mama
    - 162437 Clifton and the Kid (Box 11)
  - The Tim Conway Show
    - 0310-5421-6796 To Cuba With Love (Box 11)
    - 0311-1268-0851 Coffee Tea or Pablum (Box 11)
    - 0311-1268-0852 Triple Indemnity (Box 11)
  - Trappings
    - [no title] (Box 11)
  - Veronica's Closet
    - 225606 Veronica's Long Walk Home (Box 3A)
    - 225612 Veronica's Tattooed Man (Box 3A)
    - Cast and crew list (Box 3A)
  - Viva Valdez
    - 7-viv-75 (Pilot) (Box 11)
    - 162601 Ernesto's Scheme (Box 11)
    - 162603 Brothers' Rivalry (Box 12)
    - 162604 Mama Sees a Thief (Box 12)
    - 162602 Weekend (Box 12)
    - 162607 Papa's Legacy (Box 12)
    - 162608 My Fair Jerry (Box 12)
    - 162609 Nervous Break-Up (Box 12)
    - 162613 The Nurse's Pipes (Box 12)
    - 162614 The Apprentice (Box 12)
    - 162616 Pick Up (Box 12)
    - 162617 Mama Doesn't (Box 12)
    - 167602 Father and Son (Box 13)
    - [no number] Ernesto's Romance (Box 13)
  - We Got It Made
    - 3121 Am I Blue? (Box 13)
    - 3122 Mickey the Shoplifter (Box 13)
    - 3123 Sexiest Bachelor (Box 13)
    - 3124 David's Birthday (Box 13)
    - 3125 Mickey Goes Topless (Box 13)
    - 3126 Mickey Sleepwalks (Box 13)
    - 3127 The Boyfriend (Box 13)
    - 3128 Mickey's Mom (Box 13)
    - 3129 Mickey Gets Married part 1 (Box 13)
    - 3130 Mickey Gets Married part 2 (Box 13)
    - 3131 The Super (Box 13)
    - 3132 Mickey's T-Shirt (Box 13)
    - 3134 Mickey's Misconception (Box 13)
    - 3135 Mickey's Poster (Box 13)
    - 3136 The Other Tucker (Box 13)
    - [no number] (Pilot) (Box 13)
  - What's Happening!!
    - 0104 My Three Tons (Box 13)
  - You're An Animal Gilbert
    - [no number] (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Alan Rafkin 95/96 Directing Schedule (Box 13)
    - Bungalow 78 Productions Holiday List (Box 13)
- Videos
  - Ace Awards
    - [no title], 1990 (Box 14)
      VHS
  - Alan Rafkin Footage
    - [no title], 12/15/1980 (Box 14)
      Beta
  - Beverly Hills 90210
    - [no title], 2/17/1993 (Box 14)
  - The Boys
    - 101, 6/8/1989 (Box 14)
    - 202, 6/22/1989 (Box 14)
    - 203, 7/13/1989 (Box 14)
    - 204, 6/22/1989 (Box 14)
    - 207, 7/31/1989 (Box 14)
    - 208, 8/15/1989 (Box 14)
    - Pilot, 8/10/1988 (Box 14)
  - Charlie and Co.
    - 101, 8/15/1985 (Box 14)
      Missing, 5/2007
    - 6s01, 9/3/1985 (Box 14)
      BETA
    - 6s02, 9/3/1985 (Box 14)
    - v-11886, 4/19/1985 (Box 14)
      U-MATIC
  - Chicken Soup
    - 101, 9/5/1989 (Box 14)
    - 108, 1989 (Box 14)
    - 109, 10/22/1989 (Box 14)
    - 111, 11/20/1989 (Box 14)
  - Coach
    - 66608 (Box 14)
    - 67212, 11/25/1991 (Box 14)
    - 100 Episode Retrospective (Box 14)
    - 205 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 65521 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 66601 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 66602 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 66602 final (Box 14)
    - 66606 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 66606 final (Box 14)
    - 66607 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 66610 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 66610 final (Box 14)
    - 66611 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 66613 pcut 1 (Box 14)
    - 66616 ASSY (Box 14)
    - 66617 ASSY, might be "Puppy Love" episode (Box 14)
    - 66618 pcut 1 (Box 15)
    - 66622 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 66623 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 66624 ecut 1 (Box 15)
    - 66625 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67201 ASSY, 8/27/1991 (Box 15)
    - 67201 ASSY, 8/27/1991 (Box 15)
    - 67202 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67203 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67206 ASSY, 10/23/1991 (Box 15)
    - 67208 ASSY, 10/7/1991 (Box 15)
    - 67210 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67211 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67213 ASSY, 12/9/1991 (Box 15)
    - 67215 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67216 ASSY, 1/6/1992 (Box 15)
    - 67217 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67219 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67223 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 67225 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 68301 cut b (Box 15)
    - 68302 cut b (Box 15)
    - 68303 cut b (Box 15)
    - 68307 cut a (Box 15)
    - 68307 last scene (Box 15)
    - 68309 cut a (Box 15)
    - 68309 cut e (Box 15)
    - 68310 cut b (Box 15)
    - 68312 cut a (Box 15)
    - 68313 cut a (Box 15)
    - 68315 cut a (Box 15)
    - 68319 cut a (Box 15)
    - 68321 cut a, 2/26/1993 (Box 15)
    - 68323 cut b (Box 15)
    - 68324 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 69201 cut 1 ASSY (Box 15)
    - 69204 cut 1 (Box 15)
    - 69208 cut 1 (Box 15)
    - 69213 cut aa (Box 15)
    - 69216 cut a (Box 15)
    - 69219 cut a (Box 15)
    - 69219 final (Box 15)
    - 69224 cut a (Box 15)
    - 69227 cut 1 (Box 15)
    - 82144 cut 2 (Box 15)
    - 91-92 Gag Reel (Box 15)
    - Coaches Conference ASSY (Box 15)
    - Diamonds (Box 15)
    - Puppy Love, 1/22/1991 (Box 15)
    - The Curly O'Brien Awards (Box 15)
  - Destined to Live
    - [no title] (Box 15)
  - The Dick Van Dyke Show
    - [no title - extra copy?], 4/20/1990 (Box 15)
  - The Dick Van Dyke Show / My Favorite Martian
    - 37 / 3 (Box 15)
  - Do You Know Who I am?
    - part 1 (Box 16)
    - part 2 (Box 16)
  - Dream On
    - [no title], 6/20/1992 (Box 16)
  - Emmy Awards
    - [no title], 1982 (Box 16)
  - A Family for Joe
    - 101, 4/14/1990 (Box 16)
    - 103, 3/29/1990 (Box 16)
    - 104, 3/27/1990 (Box 16)
    - 105, 4/26/1990 (Box 16)
    - 106, 4/19/1990 (Box 16)
    - 109, 5/8/1990 (Box 16)
  - Family Man
    - [no title], 9/26/1989 (Box 16)
    - [no title], 1/4/1990 (Box 16)
  - Florence Henderson's Country Kitchen
    - [no title] (Box 16)
  - Four in Love
    - [no title], 4/11/1980 (Box 16)
  - From this Moment On
    - Pilot, 5/5/1989 (Box 16)
  - Gemini
    - part 1 (Box 16)
    - part 2 (Box 16)
  - The Ghost Writer
    - pre-tape, 2/13/1989 (Box 16)
    - run-thru, 2/10/1989 (Box 16)
    - talent test, 1/18/1989 (Box 16)
  - Giving Back
    - [no title] (Box 16)
  - Good Advice
    - 201 roughcut, 9/10/1993 (Box 18)
    - 202 roughcut, 9/24/1993 (Box 18)
    - 205 editor'scut, 12/2/1993 (Box 18)
    - 205 sweetened master, 3/11/1994 (Box 18)
  - It's Garry Shandling's Show
    - 101, 8/14/1986 (Box 16)
    - 102, 8/24/1986 (Box 16)
    - 103, 9/16/1986 (Box 17)
    - 104, 8/29/1986 (Box 17)
    - 105, 9/20/1986 (Box 17)
    - 105, 7/24/1987 (Box 17)
    - 106, 10/1/1986 (Box 17)
    - 107, 11/21/1986 (Box 17)
    - 109, 12/3/1986 (Box 17)
    - 109, 12/9/1986 (Box 17)
    - 110, 12/22/1986 (Box 17)
    - 114, 2/23/1987 (Box 17)
    - 115, 3/23/1987 (Box 17)
    - 116, 3/30/1987 (Box 17)
    - 201, 8/19/1987 (Box 17)
    - 202, 8/19/1987 (Box 17)
    - 203, 9/9/1987 (Box 17)
    - 204, 9/9/1987 (Box 17)
    - 205, 10/26//87 (Box 17)
    - 206, 11/10/1987 (Box 17)
    - 207, 12/7/1987 (Box 17)
    - 208, 12/7/1987 (Box 17)
    - 210, 1/12/1988 (Box 17)
    - 211, 2/11/1988 (Box 17)
    - 212, 1/12/1988 (Box 17)
    - 213, 1/27/1988 (Box 17)
    - 215, 2/25/1988 (Box 17)
    - 216, 3/29/1988 (Box 17)
    - 217 (Box 17)
    - 302, 12/12/1988 (Box 17)
    - 303, 10/20/1988 (Box 17)
    - 304, 11/14/1988 (Box 17)
    - 305, 11/29/1988 (Box 17)
    - 307, 12/27/1988 (Box 17)
    - 308, 12/27/1988 (Box 17)
    - 309, 12/13/1988 (Box 18)
    - 310, 2/1/1989 (Box 18)
    - 314, 2/9/1989 (Box 18)
    - 101 cut 1, 1/19/1988 (Box 18)
    - 102 cut 1, 1/19/1988 (Box 18)
    - 103 cut1, 1/19/1988 (Box 18)
    - 311 / 312, 1/27/1989 (Box 18)
    - clips (Box 18)
    - Hello Alan, Mar-89 (Box 18)
    - Live ElectionShow, 12/2/1988 (Box 18)
    - no number (Box 18)
    - [no title], 10/4/1988 (Box 18)
  - Jeff Cesario
    - Promotional (Box 18)
  - Just You and Me
    - 1, 11/6/1987 (Box 18)
    - Pilot, 4/22/1987 (Box 18)
  - L.B.J.
    - [no title] (Box 18)
  - The Larry Sanders Show
    - spider episode, 8/29/1992 (Box 18)
  - Laverne and Shirley
    - [no title] (Box 18)
  - Living in Paradise
    - [no title] (Box 18)
  - Love Boat
    - [no title] (Box 18)
  - Missoula Children's Theater
    - [no title] (Box 18)
    - [no title] (Box 18)
  - Murphy Brown
    - cut 1, 1/20/1994 (Box 18)
    - cut 1, 1/22/1994 (Box 18)
    - cut 1, 4/8/1994 (Box 18)
    - [no title], 4/21/1994 (Box 18)
  - One Day at a Time
    - 425 (Box 19)
    - 426, 3/28/1979 (Box 19)
    - 508, 11/9/1979 (Box 19)
    - 518, 2/13/1980 (Box 19)
    - 715 (Box 19)
    - optional shots of Valerie (Box 19)
  - Pair of Jokers
    - [no title] (Box 19)
  - Puppetman
    - Pilot (Box 19)
  - Sam
    - [no title], 4/1/1985 (Box 19)
    - [no title], 4/3/1985 (Box 19)
  - Scared Straight
    - [no title] (Box 19)
  - Shakiest Gun in the West
    - [no title] (Box 19)
  - Sisters
    - [no title], 7/30/1986 (Box 19)
  - Star Trek: The Next Generation
    - [no title], 5/17/1993 (Box 19)
  - Uncle Bobo's World of Fun
    - [no title] (Box 19)
  - The Verdict is Yours
    - [no title] (Box 19)
    - 1982 EmmyAwards (Box 19)
    - [no title], 7/24/1958 (Box 19)
  - Wreck Szabo
    - Pilot (Box 19)
    - viewing (Box 19)
  - A Year at the Top
    - [no title] (Box 19)
  - Young Indiana Jones Chronicles
    - [no title], 4/17/1993 (Box 19)
- Memorabilia
  - Miscellaneous (Box 20)